=Love Start From Marriage= =Episode 8=
= الحب يبدأ من الزواج = = الحلقة 8 =
What a coincidence.
يالها من صدفة.
How did you appear like that?
كيف بدت هكذا؟
I couldn't reach you.
لم أستطع الوصول إليك.
So came straight here looking for you.
لذا جئت هنا مباشرة تبحث عنك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Qianxun, it was my fault.
Qianxun ، كان خطأي.
I failed to protect you.
لقد فشلت في حمايتك.
Qianxun.
Qianxun.
Promise you won't disappear like that again.
أعدك بأنك لن تختفي هكذا مرة أخرى.
I'm worried.
انا قلق.
I won't.
أنا لن.
Cheers.
هتافات.
To be honest,
صدقا،
it's been a long long time
لقد مر وقت طويل
since I devoured food like this.
منذ أن التهمت طعامًا مثل هذا.
You're not afraid Gu Chengze found out?
أنت لست خائفًا من اكتشاف Gu Chengze؟
I suppose rich people like him,
أفترض أن الأغنياء يحبونه ،
won't show up in places like this.
لن تظهر في أماكن مثل هذه.
What do you think of him?
ما رأيك فيه؟
He is pretty good.
إنه جيد جدًا.
Cheers.
هتافات.
How much have you two drunk?
كم هل أنتما الاثنان في حالة سكر؟
Can we stop drinking?
هل يمكننا التوقف عن الشرب؟
None of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
And you.
وأنت.
Can't you behave yourself now that you're married?
ألا يمكنك أن تتصرف الآن بعد أن تزوجت؟
Let's go to another round!
دعنا نذهب إلى جولة أخرى!
Yeah!
نعم!
Here.
هنا.
You.
أنت.
Take care of the bill.
اعتني بالفاتورة.
Where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
How much did you guys drink?
كم شربتم يا رفاق؟
Rose.
ارتفع.
Isn't it the trash guy Li?
أليس رجل القمامة لي؟
Why did he also come back?
لماذا عاد ايضا؟
Exactly.
بالضبط.
Let me send him to hell!
دعني أرسله إلى الجحيم!
You're Mrs. Gu now.
أنت السيدة جو الآن.
You can't do that.
لا يمكنك فعل ذلك.
Can't you behave yourself?
لا يمكنك أن تتصرف بنفسك؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
(You don't even deserve Li Zhuo.)
(أنت لا تستحق حتى Li Zhuo.)
(Let alone Gu Chengze.)
(ناهيك عن Gu Chengze.)
(Why do you always take all the advantage?)
(لماذا تستفيد دائمًا من كل المزايا؟)
(Dream on.)
(في الحلم.)
Babe. Get in the car.
فاتنة.  اركب السيارة.
I won't.
أنا لن.
-Behave yourself. -I want more beer.
-تصرف بنفسك.  اريد المزيد من البيرة.
Get in the car.
اركب السيارة.
Stop here, please.
قف هنا من فضلك.
-I'm not getting the car. -Place your legs.
- أنا لا أحضر السيارة.  -ضع ساقيك.
Let me go.
دعني اذهب.
What's up?
ما أخبارك؟
Is V Group going broke?
هل V Group ستفلس؟
You got time to bully people, huh?
لديك وقت للتنمر على الناس ، هاه؟
I won't forget what you did today.
لن أنسى ما فعلته اليوم.
What the hell am I up against?
ما الذي أواجهه بحق الجحيم؟
How dare you beat me?
كيف تجرؤ على هزيمتي؟
You trash.
أنت قمامة.
What did you just say?
ماذا قلت للتو؟
You're not trash.
أنت لست قمامة.
You're handsome.
أنت وسيم
You're really hot.
هو حقا حار.